const questions = [
  {
    question: `Who did Dad write a letter to when he was in 7 th grade because he had a crush on her?`,
    answer: `Alyssa Milano – Who’s The Boss`
  },
  {
    question: `What holiday is exactly one week before Dad’s birthday?`,
    answer: `National Pizza Day – February 9th`
  },
  {
    question: `What movie character was so frightening that Dad had to leave the movie theater when he was five years old?`,
    answer: `Jawa – Star Wars 1978`
  },
  {
    question: `What hospital was Dad born in?`,
    answer: `Brockton Hospital`
  },
  {
    question: `What is the name of the mascot of Dad’s high school?`,
    answer: `Hilltopper - B.M.C. Durfee High School`
  },
  {
    question: `What is the name of the bait shop Dad used to go to when he was a kid?`,
    answer: `Bucko’s Bait`,
    bonus: [`where was that?`,`Cook Pond in Fall River`]
  },
  {
    question: `What happened the first-time Grandpa Louie took dad fishing?`,
    answer: `Dad dropped his fishing pole in the water because a dragon fly landed on the reel`
  },
  {
    question: `What did Dad ask Grandpa Louie after he fell in the water while fishing at the Swansea Dam?`,
    answer: `Does this mean we are not going for ice cream?`
  },
  {
    question: `How old was Dad when he moved to Fall River?`,
    answer: `Three years old`
  },
  {
    question: `What two towns did Dad live in before moving to Fall River?`,
    answer: `Holbrook and Somerset`
  },
  {
    question: `What was the name of the street or neighborhood Dad lived in in Somerset?`,
    answer: `Calvin Avenue or Americana Terrace`
  },
  {
    question: `What was the make and model of Dad’s first car?`,
    answer: `Ford Escort`
  },
  {
    question: `What happened to Dad’s first car?`,
    answer: `It got totaled in Newport one night on the way to Jai Alai`
  },
  {
    question: `What school was Dad banned from when he was in college?`,
    answer: `Wheaton`
  },
  {
    question: `What did Dad compliment the first time he met Mom?`,
    answer: `Her eyes`
  },
  {
    question: `What were the names of the two dogs Dad had growing up?`,
    answer: `Sam and Buddy`
  },
  {
    question: `How did the family end up with Sam the dog?`,
    answer: `Uncle Freddy showed up with him one day`
  },
  {
    question: `What happened to Sam the dog?`,
    answer: `Hit by a car`
  },
  {
    question: `What were the names of the two cats Dad had growing up?`,
    answer: `Marbles and Freckles`
  },
  {
    question: `What happened to the two cats Dad had growing up?`,
    answer: `Marbles died on Christmas morning after drinking antifreeze on the garage floor and Freckles ran away`
  },
  {
    question: `What was the name of the street Dad grew up on?`,
    answer: `Woodlawn Street`
  },
  {
    question: `Where was Mom and Dad’s first kiss?`,
    answer: `In the alley next to the Z-Bar`
  },
  {
    question: `What was Dad’s major in college?`,
    answer: `Accounting`
  },
  {
    question: `One time when he was mad, what did Grandpa Louie throw at Dad?`,
    answer: `A bowling ball`
  },
  {
    question: `What instrument did Dad take lessons in when he was in elementary school?`,
    answer: `Flute`
  },
  {
    question: `Why did Dad decide to take up his first instrument?`,
    answer: `Because there were lots of girls signing up for lessons`
  },
  {
    question: `What did Dad hang in his car every Christmas when he was a teenager?`,
    answer: `Mistletoe`
  },
  {
    question: `What three jobs did Dad do before he had a driver’s license to earn money?`,
    answer: `Cut grass, umpired little league, and was a DJ`
  },
  {
    question: `What was dad’s first real job when he turned 16?`,
    answer: `He worked at WYC as a steward, lifeguard, and sailing instructor`
  },
  {
    question: `What was the name of the first company Dad worked for after college?`,
    answer: `Medical Image Management`
  },
  {
    question: `What state did Dad bribe his way out of while on that job?`,
    answer: `Texas`
  },
  {
    question: `What happened to Dad’s face one time when Dad was winter hiking with Grumpa?`,
    answer: `Frostbite`
  },
  {
    question: `What was Grumpa’s reaction when he saw Dad’s frostbitten face when they were winter hiking?`,
    answer: `He said “Ooooffff!”`
  },
  {
    question: `What did Grumpa do after he said “Ooooffff” after seeing Dad’s frostbitten face?`,
    answer: `He gave Dad ointment and hot chocolate`
  },
  {
    question: `Has Dad ever stood up for someone at their wedding?  If so, who?`,
    answer: `Yes, Best Man for Michael Terceira. Yes, Man of Honor or Honor Attendant for Auntie Amy.`
  },
  {
    question: `What was the name of the Church Dad attended growing up?`,
    answer: `Holy Name`
  },
  {
    question: `What was the name of Dad’s college mascot?`,
    answer: `Chieftain`
  },
  {
    question: `What is Dad’s college mascot called now?`,
    answer: `Skyhawk`
  },
  {
    question: `What did Glamma make for Dad as a special treat for breakfast every now and then?`,
    answer: `Banana pancakes`
  },
  {
    question: `One time when Grandpa Louie was watching Dad and Auntie Amy they ordered a pizza – why did Grandpa Louie send it back?`,
    answer: `He saw a piece of onion on the pizza`
  },
  {
    question: `Does Dad have any Godchildren?`,
    answer: `Yes, Cole Terceira and Caroline`
  }
];